■
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
最新最快的HR-HDTV 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.60,0:00:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,■
翻译:  blueliongb  双字幕:  blueliongb   后期:  Dragon
■
很明显我对有些事判断错误
Obviously I miscalculated a few things.
为什么在你即将心想事成时
Why is it that the moment your life exceeds your wildest dreams.
却又总被搅了好事
The knife appears in your back.
我来告诉你件事
Well I'll tell you one thing.
我绝不会让他们碰我一根汗毛
I will never let them touch me.
我的邻居一定打开门对我抱怨了
My neighbor must have open the door to complain.
对于智商上千的我来说  肯定错过了一些东西
For a guy with a 4 digit IQ, I must have missed something...
但错过的并不太多
but I haven’t missed much.
我几乎就要成为影响世界的人了
I come this close to having an impact the world.
然而现在唯一能做的  看来只有撞击人行道
And now the only thing I have impact on. Was the sidewalk.
永无止境
看见那家伙了吗
You seethat guy?
那就是不久前的我
That was me, Not so long ago.
一个毒酒不沾的人为何这个样子
what kind of guy, without a drug or alcohol problem looks this way?
除非是个作家
Only a writer.
奇怪的是没有人相信我刚签了一本新书合约
strangely enough, nobody believe that! actually had a book contract.
他是一种新型变型核因子  真的是我个人创作
He was disguised as a novel NF but it was really my personal manifesto.
在21世纪是很独特的
individuals in the 21 century.
创建一个乌托邦社会  我们都是某种...
Creating a utopian society, where are all sort a...
这真是...  这真是个...
It really is... It really is. A...
今天我一定要发威
Today was the day, I gonna kick its ass.
灵感来吧  来吧
Here we go, here we go...
会很精彩的
It's gonna be great.
只需要投入时间  坐在房间里
only need to invest time sifting in the room.
这是成功的关键
That's the key concept.
大门不出
Don't leave the room.
几个星期这样过去了
A few weeks passed this way.
或许是几个月
Maybe a few months.
至少我还有林迪
At least I still had Lindi.
就这样?
Just like that?
算了吧  爱迪...
Come on, Eddie...
我不觉得这令人惊讶
This is hardly a surprise.
我很惊讶
I'm surprised.
不要这样
Let's just not do this.
我准备在星期五交稿
I am gonna hand in 90 pages tomorrow or friday...
先看她如何说吧
if you just wait to see what she says.
-爱迪  -什么?
- Eddie! - What?
我知道事情将会怎样  我是  曾经是你的女朋友
I know how it's going. I am ... I was your girlfriend.
女朋友已不足以形容你
This word doesn't even begin to describe what you are to me.
伙伴  借贷公司
Partner? Squeeze?
恋人  情妇
Paramour. Inamorata
清洁工  提款机
Cleaning Lady. Bank.
即使这样
Even so...
你要知道
What's mine is yours too.
我会给你所有我将来拥有的  甚至后半生
And you know that I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
其实我有想过  我们也许应该...
In fact, I was thinking, that we should probably...
不要求婚
Don't propose!
为什么不?
Why not?
因为你曾经的婚姻太"美好"了
Because it worked out so "well" for you last time.
的确如此  我刚毕业就和梅利莎结婚了
it's true, I was married once, right out of college to melissa.
我愿意
I do.
可是很短暂
Briefly.
这样不行
This isn't working.
虽然你说的都是事实  但我仍然爱你
Well even though everything you said is true, I still love you.
我得回去工作
I gotta get back to work.
你还没有告诉我怎么回事
You didn't even tell me what happened.
-我得到那份工作了  -真的?
- I got it! - You did?
真的  我现在是名编辑
Hum, I am an editor.
有自己的助手  相信吗?
I'll have my own assistant. You believe that?
当然相信  你应得的
Yea, Of course I believe you. You deserve it.
谢谢
Thanks.
她当时是对的  为什么要容忍?
She was right. Why stick it out.
我刚错过了机会
I had clearly missed my own chance.
我童年记得的
We both knew what was backing.
在新泽西州老家  在我房间的下铺
The lower bunk of my childhood bedroom in Jersey.
爸爸邀请我加入
My Father happy to welcome me into...
一个牙齿实验
the challenging field of dental supply inventory.
爱迪・莫拉
Eddie Morra!
所有跟你没有多余关系的人
Of all the useless relationships better forgot and put away in mothballs.
最好把他忘记  我的前小舅子
Is there any more useless than the ex-brother in law?
这么巧  多久没见了?  九年了
Holy Shit, man! How long it's been? Nine years?
你还好吗?  看起来你像个流浪汉
Are you alright? You look like you livin' on the streets.
怎么回事
What's going on?
没什么  我在写作
Not much. Ehmm, I am writing... writing a lot.
你还在尝试写作?
Oh, you still trying to write?
事实上  我跟书商已经有合约
In a matter of fact, I have a book contract
-真的?  那很好  -是的
- Really? It's great. - Yes.
你呢  还在做药品生意?
What abou you? Still dealing?
我看起来像是还在买卖药品?
Do I look like I am still dealing?
不不  当然不
No, you don't, no, no.
走吧  去喝一杯  聊聊你的书
Come on, let's get a drink I wonna hear about this book.
下午2点  太早了吧
I don't know, it's two o'clock in the afternoon.
几时起你也在乎喝酒时间了?
And when does that ever stopped you?
好吧
Well.
梅利莎现在怎么样
So, so how is Melissa doing?
-给你  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
我不可能知道  没见她
I wouldn't know, I don't see her.
她搬到了北部
She moved upstate.
在家做网上销售的工作
She got some internet-home-sales kinda job.
有2个孩子
Couple of kids.
2个孩子  丈夫是谁?
Couple of kids. Who is the husband?
真想知道的话  那个人已经离开了她
He walked out on her, if you really wonna know.
你会在乎吗  老兄
What do you care, man?
你们的婚姻好象仅持续了5分钟
You were married for like five minutes.
我不想谈她  说说你吧
I don't wonna talk about her. I want to talk about you.
说说你的书进展如何
Tell me about this book. How's it going?
比原定计划慢了  没赶上进度
Well it's a.... I am behind, I am behind on my book...
-你写多少了?  -一个字也没写
- How much you already written of it? - Not one word.
-创作问题是吗  -是的
- Creative problems, uhm? - Yeah.
我想我可以帮忙  只此一次
I suppose, I can help you with that. Just this once.
别  别  别...
Oh, no, no, no...
你甚至还不知道是什么
You do not even know what it is.
-你还在买卖药品  -兄弟  我一早就转行了
- You still dealing. - Brother, I am lightyears from that now.
现在我在一家制药公司作咨询工作
I've been doing some consultung for a pharmaceutical company.
在地下工厂造假伟哥  算了吧
On a magic lab for fake viagra... come on.
不  这是一个独家产品  明年上市
No. This is an exclusive product. This coming on the streets next year.
通过了临床试验  已得到联邦食品药监局认可
Adopted by clinical tests and approved by the FDA.
只是出于好奇
Just out of curiosity and that's all...
让我看看
Let me see.
里面是什么?
What's in it?
他们发现了激活大脑潜能的方法
They've identified these receptors in the brain that actived specific circus.
据说人只能运用大脑20%的能力
And you know how they say that we can only access 20% of our brain.
这药可使大脑100%运作
All of this does. It let you access all of it.
弗恩  看着我  我跟你一样吗?
Vernon, look at me. Do I looked like you?
我虽然萎靡不振  意志消沉
I'm broken, I'm depressed of my ass.
但我不认为夸夸其谈和毒品能让我的生活
I do not think that my life can take some sudden of spring,
发生突然转变  变得出名  富有
famous, fortune, by taking a shiny brags and drug.
是的  什么时候
Yes. When?
告诉他  我不能这样做
Tell him I can not do that.
不  你告诉他  就现在
No. Do tell. No, now!
恐怕我现在必须离开了
I'm afraid I must leave you now.
但我真的还想再跟你聊聊  打电话给我
But I really do wonna do this again, so call me.
这个算是礼物
And that's on the house.
我不想要
I do not want it.
别没良心
Do not be ungrateful.
你知道价格吗  一颗8百美元  吓人吧
You know how much it costs? 800 bucks. Pop!
不用客气
You're welcome.
回家的路上  我想着梅利莎
On the way home, I thought about Melissa.
她怎么也成了失败者呢
How can she be a failure too?
她很聪明  比身边的任何人都聪明
She been so smart. Smarter than anyone around her.
显然这必定跟爱迪有直接关系
Clearly, there was directline between this Eddie.
下午三点就有些醉
Slightly drunk at three o'clock and other things.
吐在他老板的桌上
vomiting on the boss' desk...
或是偷吗啡自杀
or steal morphine of dying.
怎能怪琳达抛弃我呢
So who can blame Linda for dumping me.
说到底  一颗药丸还能让我糟到哪里去
In the end, how much worse could it get?
我不想见到任何人
I don't want to see anybody.
尤其是房东那年青而又令人厌恶的妻子
Especially not my landlord's nasty young wife.
-瓦莱丽  周二  -够了  够了
- Valerie, on Tuesday ... - No, enough, ok?
史帝夫来收租金的话  你可以跟他瞎编
Steve handles the rent, so you can fed your crap to him!
我突然有了别的理由摆脱她
I suddenly had extra reason to get away from her.
我草率的吞下了药丸
I had thoughtlessly ingested a substance.
付他妈的房租
Pay the damn rent!
我开始知道这药的作用
I got remarkably little information from Veron about what this drug would do.
你甚至可以找份邮件快递工作来付房租
you can even be a biker messanger and come up with that .
如果是迷幻药怎么办
What if it's a hallucinogen?
真是可悲
It's pathetic!
我的天
Oh My God!
发作的时候还要听她说话  我可能会跳窗
Listening to her rag when I was triping, I would jump out of the window.
回神  你在听我说吗
Hello? Are you listening to me?
知道吗  你很快会被赶出去
Do you get it? You gonna be out on the streets!
接着我感觉到了
And then I felt it.
就象盲人复明一般
I was blind, but now I see.
-怎么回事?  -什么?
- What's wrong? - What?
你不喜欢我  我不怪你
You do not like me and I dont blame you.
你认为我是一个失败者
You think I am a loser,
一个只会欠你老公房钱的失败者
who doesn't pay his rent and is sponging out your husband.
你巴不得我饮弹自尽
You whishing I blow my brain out.
但我的存在不应该让你这么沮丧
but my existence shouldn't make you this upset.
-究竟什么原因?  -不关你的事
- What is it? - That's none of your business!
法律学校的课程有问题
Something wrong in Law school?
你怎么知道我在读法律学校
How do you know I am in law school?
谁没事会拿着一本已逝大法官的书
People normally not carrying around dry concipated academical books about a dead supreme court justice.
你偷偷摸摸跟踪我
You are a creep! You been following me.
不  我看到那本书
No, I just noticed the book.
你只看到了个书角  怎么会知道
You saw only a corner. How did you know that?
我以前看到过  12年前上大学时
I've seen it before. 12 years ago in college...
坐在沙发上想着做爱
sitting on the couch and wanted to make sex.
等着她走出浴室
I was waiting for her coming out of the bathroom,
希望她有保险套
hoping she'd have a condom.
不知怎的  我的潜意识
Somehow, my subconscious has served this up.
让我回想起这些记忆
A memory I wouldn't even recorded.
一些我以为忘记了的记忆变得即取即用
It was there the whole time and all I need was the access.
如果你想写论文  这本书不合适
If you writing a paper, thats not the book I'd use.
谁问你的意见了?
Who asked you?
就从那儿开始吧  黑斯廷处理过很多案子
Hasting has its own history, I'd start there.
有趣的是这家伙是个白痴
Interesting point dramatically, this guy was an idiot...
他大部分的理论观点都是由被他解雇的秘书写的
which gives increased theory that one of the clerks he has fired actually wrote most this guy's major oponions.
你用谷歌搜索他秘书的儿子  他们很乐意谈论自己的父亲
You google the clerk's sons. They love to talk to you on their dad.
他们能告诉你一些别人都不知道的事情
They give you something that no one else says.
这样你便有一些比别人特别的课题
So you have something that no one has... information from the museum show,
只要大略的阅读
half read article some PBS docomentory.
知识点就会出现在眼前  并且自己融汇
It was all bubbling up of my front... mixing itself together...
混合成一杯极好的资讯鸡尾酒
into a sparkling cocktail of useful information.
她没有机会(拒绝我)
She didn't have a chance.
那你有什么建议
So, what are your suggestions?
我们当然也有做她的论文
We really worked on her paper too.
45分钟就完成了一篇很棒的论文
In 45 minutes, it was a polish jam.
她非常的愉快
She was pleased.
家
Home.
这不可能是我的家  可能吗?
But it couldn't be my home, could it!?
谁会象这样生活?
Who would live like this?
真想一把火烧掉这一切
First thought was torching.
但我还有理智
But, sanity prevailed.
这是到底是什么药?  我不敢相信
What was this drug? I couldn't stay messy on it.
我已经6个小时没有抽烟  也没进食
I hadn't had a cigarette in 6 hours, I hadn't eaten.
但我感觉神清气爽  究竟是什么?
So, I am steamiest and tidy. What was this?
象毒品一样强化感官?
A drug for people, who wonna be more heino retentive?
我没有幻觉  不觉得怪异  只觉得头脑清醒
I wasn't high, wasn't wired, just clear.
我知道需要做什么  怎样做
I knew what I needed to do, and how to do it.
第二天早上  当我开始思索时
The next morning, I send a little probe down into my brain.
感觉脑袋不灵光了
No signs of brilliance came up to gravy.
我被打回原形
In short, I was back.
但有些东西保留了下来
But something remained.
-你在开玩笑吗?  -没有
- Are you kidding. - No
-白纸生出字来?  -是的
- Words have appeared on paper... - Yes.
-你写的  -您看3页吧
- Written by you? - All I ask you to do, is to read 3 pages.
就看3页
Just read 3 Pages in the next hour.
如果你读不下去  我退还您的预付款
and if you don't want to keep reading, I give you back the advance.
行  爱迪  忙你的去
OK, Eddie. Go ahead.
爱迪  到家给我打个电话
Eddie, give me a call, when you get in.
爱迪  我读了40多页  给我打电话
Eddie, I am 40 pages further in. call me.
这的确有点意思  我仍在读
This is a little crip odd, but I am still reading.
好吧  你是如何办到的?
Ok, how did you do this?
我真的喜欢  到家赶快给我来电  好吗
I'd really like... call me the minute you get it! Call, ok?
-是谁?  -弗恩  是爱迪
- Who is it? - Vernon, its Eddie.
-哪个爱迪?  -莫拉
- Eddie who? - Morra.
来的不是时候  爱迪
Not a good time, Eddie.
弗恩  我真的需要的和你谈谈
Hey Vern, I just really need to talk to you.
-弗恩  发生了什么  -别担心  我没事
- Vern, what happened? - Don't worry about it, I'm fine.
爱迪  你终于感兴趣了?
So, Eddie, you are interested after all.
这东西太神奇了
The stuff is amazing.
聪明人服用效果更好
Works better, if you are already smart.
弗恩  谁把你打伤的?
Vernon, who did this to you?
别打听了
Trust me, you do not want to know.
那个药叫什么名字
So what is this called?
还没有正式名字
Still no name on the street.
厨子都叫它NZT-48
However, boys in the kitchen, are calling it NZT-48.
厨子  听起来没得到药监局批准
Boys in the "kitchen" ? Doesn't sound very FDA approved.
药监局批准?  那都是骗人的  你会相信?
FDA-approved. That's a lie. You didn't believe this shit, did you?
好了  我了解到的是
OK, what we have here,
一个很久不见  极不可靠的家伙
some unknown, untested, possibly dangerous drug...
从身份不明的实验室里骗出一些
scammed out of some unidentifed lab somewhere,
未经测试的不明危险药物
given to me by a highly unrealible guy I hadn't seen in years.
你还想要更多?
So do you want more?
要  肯定要
Yes, definitely.
好的  我们谈谈  不过我现在需要你帮忙
Alright, we'll talk about it. But I need a favour first.
你瞧  这个样子我可没法出去
Obviously, I am in no condition to go out right now.
所以如果你能下去
So I was wondering if you could pop down...
到干洗店把我的西装取回来
at drycleaners and grab my suit for me.
再弄点早餐来
And maybe grab a little breakfast for us.
他知道我会去的
He knew, he had me.
没问题
Sure.
从现在起  我会高兴的听他差遣
From now on, I'd be happily be his errand boy.
帮他擦窗  洗厕所
Wash his windows, scrab his toilets.
替他做任何事  只为得到他的药丸
Anything I can do, to get my hands on this little clear pill...
成为强化版爱迪
that would bring back... enchanced Eddie.
弗恩
Vern?
911  有什么紧急情况
911, what's you emergency?
我要报告...  一起谋杀
Hi, I need to report... a murder.
是的  7B
7B, yes.
我不会离开的
OK, I won't.
他们花了很长时间才到达
It took them forever.
我站在那里  开始明白...
And the longer I stood there, the clearer I saw.
弗恩一早就知道对方会找上门
Vern had know, whoever had done this.
而对方找上门的原因只有一个
And one guess, what they have been looking for.
但他们找到了吗
But have they found it?
如果在家里做饭  我也没命了
Shit. You are a cook, I'd be dead too.
警察  请开门
Police department. Open the door please.
警察  快开门
Police department. Open the door.
请开门
Open the door please!
警察  开门
Police! Open the door!
快开门
Open the door!
-露出双手  -我是报警的人
- Let me see your hands! - No, no. I'm the caller. I called you guys!
你们是老朋友  经常在一起?
So you guys been tight? Hang out a lot?
他是我前妻的弟弟
He is the brother of my ex-wife.
我在街上遇到他  他让我去他那里
I met him on the street and he asked me to come up.
-买毒品?  -不是  为什么这么问?
- To buy drugs? - No! No. What?
这家伙做什么的
What did this guy do?
我不知道  他是...
He was... I do not know. He was a...
他是个古董商
He was a antiques dealer.
-商人  -对  古董商人
- A dealer? - Yes. Antiques.
椅子以及别的东西
Like a, like be any just kind of a... chairs.
那些弧形木椅腿
You know lika a curved wooden legs, things.
是
Yeah.
没错
That's correct.
爱德华・莫拉  他在这
Edward Morra. He is here.
受害者的姐姐
The victim's sister.
我十年没听到她的声音了
I haven't heard her voice more than ten years.
爱迪
Eddie.
梅利莎
Melissa.
你当时在那里
You were there?
昨天我在街上遇见他
Just before I met him on the street, and... yeah.
我的天
Oh my God!
我并不吃惊  他牵扯进一些事里
I wish, I was more surprised, he was involved in some stuff.
我还是别说了
I better not to say any more.
对  别说了
No, no. It's a bad idea.
我们也许应该见一面  行吗?
So we should probably meet or something, right?
不知道  我要忙葬礼
I don't know. I gotta do the funeral and...
谁知道还有什么别的事
gods know what else something.
我们不能见面  知道了吗
We can't meet, ok?
好吧  那我们还是在葬礼上见吧
Ok, I guess I'll see you at the funeral then...
不  我不想见你  请别来
No! I don't, I don't want that. Please don't.
等忙完了我会打给你
I'll call you with some point when this is over.
-好的  那就这样  -嗯
- Ok. All right. - Ok.
有些问题还没弄清  留下你的电话号码
Something is not clear here. Put down your number.
也许还要联系你
We may contact you later.
值得冒险
Worth the risk?
是你的话会怎么做
What would you do?
弗恩的现金  还有那喷涌而出的空前的脑动力
Vern's cash, combined with unprecedented surge motivation...
让我在四天内完成我的书
enabled me to finish the book in 4 days.
一天一颗  能做到的永无止境
A tablet a day, and what I can do with my day was limitless.
三天内学会弹钢琴
I learned to play the piano in three days.
数学变得有用  有趣
Math became useful and fun.
全押
I'm all in there.
甚至随便听听外语就能流利的说
Even half listing to any language had became fluid.
所以  你认为莎士比亚甘于平凡?
So Shakespeare empower mediocrity?
不和你争
There is no argue with you.
这很棒
This was great.
海伦已确定患上肿瘤
So mama has been doing research on Helen's tumors.
而根据医学纪录  这个病
And it's totally clear that anybody will familiar with Dumas Pere Porthos...
须要用到铂基药物
should be suffer mining Platinum base double gradual mental,
结合环戊烯酮酸去治疗
if I could have some ciclopentane acid.
突然间  我明白了一切的一切
I suddenly knew everything about everything.
当然  还有一个暂时性增长
Of course, there is a temporary increase,
但两年后便会崩溃
but then the collapse of the action is complete after two years.
不会  因为有防护措施
No, cause there are safeguards.
反侵略扩张?  那不存在的
Against the aggressive expansion?
人性中并没有防护措施
There aren't. 'cause there are no safeguards in human nature.
我们离题太远了
We are wired to overreach.
每个国家历史上都有法律和城墙
Look at history, all the countries has rules and wall.
葡萄牙曾拥有庞大的船队
Portugal with his big massive navy.
他们现在得到的却是袜子和廉价的保险套
All they got now are socks and cheap condoms.
英国人的想法更可笑
Or the British in their costumes.
没有人认为:  嘿  我们做得相当好
Nobody thinks: hey we are doing pretty well.
我们有朋友  有家园
We got friends, we got home,
在瑞士银行的帐户里有大笔金钱
we got a big swiss bank account.
"不要在冬季里入侵俄罗斯
You know what? "Let's not invade Russia in winter.
咱们回家喝啤酒吧  利息就够花了"
Let's go home, let's pop a beer, let's live in all the interests".
是的
Yes.
我的大脑充满了讯息
My brain was full of such things.
所有我读过的  听过的  看过的
Everything I've ever read, heard, seen...
都井井有条等待调用
was now organized and availible...
就这样喷涌而出
here it is, here you go.
爱迪
Eddie!
我肯定你有一个投资组合  若没有
Listen, I'm sure you have a portfolio but if not,
我非常有兴趣和你一起工作
I'd be very interested working with you.
好  凯文
Good, Kevin.
我交了新朋友  他们邀请我到海滩游玩
I made new friends who invited me to the beach.
不是附近的海滩
The beach... was not nearby.
我不再畏惧  不再害羞
All my fear, all my shyness... gone.
越来越大胆
But it was not enough for me to relax.
唯一的问题是  如果停止前进
only problem, if I wasn't moving forward.
我感觉自己会爆炸
I felt like I was going to explode.
-有人跳过吗  -你疯了吗?
- Anybody ever jumped? - Are you crazy?
-他要跳下去  -不  他不会跳的
- He is gonna do it. - No, he is not gonna do it.
我的天
God!
然后  我开始有个想法
Then I began to form an idea.
突然  我知道我应该怎么做
Suddenly, I knew exactly What I need to do.
不是写作  不是出书
It wasn't writing. It wasn't books.
比这更重要的事
It was much bigger than that
但需要钱才能实现
But it will take money to get there.
熊市的时候  没有人能赚很多钱
In the down market, nobody was making much.
那是因为没人有NZT
But no one had NZT.
用弗恩的8百块  我一天就赚了2千
With Vern's last 800 Dollars, I made $ 2,000 in a day.
第二天  7千5百
Next days, 7500.
太慢了
It was too slow.
我需要更多的资金
I'd need more capital.
银行不会借钱给我这样的人
Banks wont lending the guys like me.
他坐在那边的角落
He is in the corner back there.
丽芙告诉过你吧  我想借笔短期贷款
Liv told you that I want a short-term loan?
是的  我当时回话说  算了吧
Yes, and I said - forget it.
为什么?
Why?
我从没见过你  而且还没喜欢上你
Because I never seen you before and I don't like you already.
为什么要给你10万元?
Why would I give you 100,000 Dollars?
因为我能在4天翻倍
Because I quintuple my money 4 days in a row.
-你知道如何钻空子?  -不是钻空子
- So you got a fix on the game? - No, not a fix.
我用图表分析做了一些预测
I was able to calculate, sir. In pattern of use geogrphics.
如果你看看第四列  这是最初...
If you look at column four, This was the first...
被你看出来了
You're good.
好吧  这是钻空子
Ok, its a fix.
如果你被抓了打算怎么办
Yea, but when you get caught, what you gonna do then?
通常我不会记下谁借过钱给我
Well it's not as I if have a black book with your name in it,
还有  我很确定你是我惹不起的人
and besides, I get the strong feeling that you are not somebody I want to disappoint.
不要起来  我说不要起来  坐下
Do not get up. I said don't get up, sit down!
拿了钱  你就属于我了  明白吗
Ok, you take this, and you are mine, you understand?
若你不还  你知道会发生什么?
You don't pay, you know what we do?
我会把你的肚子割开
I cut you at waist,
扯出你的肠子在你的脖子上打结
peel your skin up over your head and tie a knot in it.
你不会马上丧命  但最终窒息而亡
You dont't die from this, You suffocate.
祝你好运
Good luck.
我的新朋友  凯文・多伊尔  他教我怎样
My new friend, Kevin Doyle show me how you can get...
在一个交易日内赚取2倍半的利润
two and a half time your cash at day trade firm.
这一周来我一直在服用
I've been up the dose for over a week.
药物似乎加速了我的学习进度
It seemd to cut my learning curve.
为什么买入?  那公司的CEO正面临起诉
Why you buying this? The CEO ist just being indicted.
但并未对外发放防范信息
But not for the big fat defensive contract he bribed into.
或许内部被贿赂
That's still on.
下周一应该会公布
It should be announced next week.
我沉浸其中  忘我的亢奋
I was jacked in, booted up.
最后一周完结前  我的银行帐户
At the end of week, My brokerage account...
已超过2百万美元
contained over two million dollars.
消息迅速蔓延
Word quickly got out.
你有19个消息
You have 19 messages.
4间公司的工作邀请  银行也将信用额度提高
four job offers, My bank raising my let credit...
纽约邮报访问
reporter from the New York Post...
明天请打电话给我  没人能那么快赚钱
Please call me back tomorrow, no one makes money that fast.
不管回不回应  文章都将刊登
Article will be published with or without you.
最后  凯文・多伊尔装作偶然地告诉我
And finally, Kevin Doyle trying to sound casual.
爱迪  我跟我老板谈过你  也许可能
Edi, I was talking you to my boss and will be a possible have a...
安排你与卡尔・万隆会面
We got you a meeting with Karl van Loon.
卡尔・万隆想跟你会面
Karl van Loon wants to meet you?
似乎是这样
Apparently so.
但你不擅长金融
You know what's a finance gift.
你能帮卡尔・万隆做些什么?
What can you do for Karl van Loon?
什么时候会说意大利语了
Since when do you speak italian?
什么事都会改变的
All has changed for the better.
我猜  自己清醒了
I guess, someone gave me a wakeup call.
我希望你不是为我而改变
I hope you didn't do it for me.
不  我只是想向你道歉
No, I just wanted to apologize to you.
我想让你知道  我不会再自暴自弃
And let you know that apparently my capacity for self-sabotage wasn't boundless after all.
问题是  你为什么要放弃我?
The real question is why did you ever put up with me?
我当时是爱你的
I was in love with you.
你的书何时面世?
So when does the book come out?
下一年  你的新助手怎样了?
Next year. How is your new assistant?
她很好
She is good.
那...  你打算...
And... are you gonna getting a...
知道吗  你跟我在一起  我很高兴
You know? I'm really happy you're here with me.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
而且...
And...
有一点点害怕你
And a little intimidated.
我们再一次开始(恋爱)
We started up again.
在她家
Her place.
在我家
My place.
任何地方
Basiclly every place.
"三天的掠夺式交易  不明身份的莫拉先生"
"In a seizing three days trading, the unknown Mr. Morra...
"莫须有的市场  《顶端提示》卡特伦・曼多发表评论说"
trumped the market, Prompting One Top Katron Mando to comment."
"他是魔术师  他是先知  "
"He is Houdini, he is a prophet of our times. "
行了  给我
OK, give me that.
-他是神?  -晚一点来我家?
- He is god!? - You coming over later?
去不了  我没有钥匙
I can't. I don't have a key.
想起来了
Oh, that's right.
我可以要回来吗
Can I have it back?
-不  -不?
- No - No?
一定要那间公寓的钥匙?  新公寓的钥匙可以吗
I mean, does it have to be that key? Can it be a new key?
我们的公寓
Our place.
性价比问题
It'll be cost-effective.
你觉得我不实际
And you say I am not practical.
我送你上班
Can I walk you to work?
亲爱的  在看什么?
What are you doing, honey?
没什么
Nothing.
你该睡了
You should sleep.
明天不是要跟卡尔・万隆会面吗
Isn't your Van Loon meeting tomorrow?
爱迪
Edi?
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
你上次吃饭是什么时候?
When is the last time you ate something?
你在这  报纸上都是你
Here it is. Nice Article on the post.
他在路上
He is on his way.
我警告你  他很善变
Now be warned, he is mercurial.
一分钟前当你是朋友  下一分钟就能吃了你
One minute your best friend, the next you are lapper.
他需要直接的答案
And he needs direct answers.
一个错误  你便会失去机会
One mistake, and you have lost him forever.
我认为我们要预演一次
I think we should act out some scenarios.
我在进餐  凯文
I am eating, Kevin.
我说  你准备好了吗?
Hey, are you ready for this?
你肯定吗?  我的前途都在这了
Are you sure? 'cause I got a little bit line here.
何不吃份吐司
Have a toast here.
-约翰  -卡尔  很高兴见到你
- John. - Hi, Karl. Good to see you.
-你好  -爱迪
- How are you? - Eddie.
爱迪・莫拉  你的秘密是什么?
So, Eddie Morra, What is your secret?
配方
Medication.
我服用特殊的配方
I am on special medication.
是吗
Yeah.
有一套方法复杂的公式
There is a formula with a complex method,
当然研究也不可或缺  大量的研究
but of course research was a component, massive research.
我对所投资的公司了如指掌  其一举一动尽在眼底
I knew absolutely everything, every move the companies that I bought.
我办公室内的文件堆得有喜马拉雅山那么高
Papers stack up like the Himalaya in my office.
你知道为什么吗?
And you know what?
-股价上涨  -间不容发
- The stocks went up. - By a hair.
当然  股票价格已经上涨  谁还愿意做那些
Sure the stocks rolls, but who wants to do all that work for...
琐碎的  微不足道的事
a shitty little optic?
短期持有不能增加人们的期望
That's not the grow people expect from a short-time holding.
我偏向于听信传闻和流言
So I dispensed with the hard statics and went through to rumor mails.
你根据传闻和流言来投资?
So your investments are based on the tom-tom speaking industry?
是的  股价并不是真的根据一个公司的运营状况变动
Sure.The shareprice is not really basing how a company works.
而是由散户的心理决定
Its about how mass psychology works.
所以如果我发现确定的计算方法能预测股票走向的话
So, if I found certail algorithms to predict how stocks grow...
制造流言就是你所谓的散户心理
Pattery-ignition, that's your psychology.
不能这么说  这模式不是每个人都能理解
Well, not everybody understands the patterns.
这的确有效
And that give me a little bit more optic,
但这只是部分窍门  所以我还去了3号门
but it's a partly trick, so that why I went on Door Number 3.
Door Number 3: 美国德克萨斯州奥斯丁市的一家广告代理商
你是说它是终极公式?
You really implying that it's some sort of ultimate formula?
他只用了10天时间就将资产从1万2千增长到2百30万
He went from 12,000 to 2.3 million in ten days.
皮尔斯先生  我确实有个公式
I do have a formula, Mr. Pierce.
大妄想
Delusion of grandeur.
我没有大妄想  只有大秘诀
I have no delusion of grandeur. I have a actural recipe for grandeur.
爱迪  我不知道你是什么人  在玩什么把戏
I don't know who you are, Eddie. And what your game is.
但我能肯定  你的处事方式和我不同
But I'm sure one thing, you don't work in my world.
在我认识的投资者中
I was surrounded by investors...
你是独特的一个
and you have no lines which shows the pride and fear which is...
这并不代表我更喜欢你的方式
not the style I like yours any better,
但你的方式的确是我们不曾见过的
but it is obvious picture you style which we haven't seen before.
看看这些公司  告诉我你的想法
Take a look this companies, tell me what do you think.
-现在?  -是的  慢慢看
- Right now? - Yes. take your time.
没问题
Sure.
这些公司都是分散的  对吗
These companies aren't the question, are they?
解释一下
Explain.
除非你两面讨好
Unless you playing both sides of the fence...
掌控整个能源
control the whole power actual a lot.
不对  通过并购市场是没法做到的
No, these companies wouldn't get you there in a merging market.
你也许会...
You would have... Oh! wow!
这一定是次非常大的合并
This must be some big-ass merger you count to plating.
只有一家公司会对
And there really only one company would love blame...
与万隆合并有异议
justify the merger with Van Loon associates.
谁告诉你的?
Who've you been talking to?
我只是分析细节  汉克・艾德伍德真的会加入合并?
Oh, I am just connacting the dots. Hank Ed Wood would really go for it?
不管你是个杰出的骗子  还是思维敏捷的年青人
Whether you are amazing con nor you are a so smart young man....
你们俩一起...
Come on! The two of you together...
全世界都不得不来乞求能源
The whole world have to come begging for...
就象哈沃・特斯尼斯自吹为大师般不遗余力
energy like Hover Twisness blowed guru.
回到主题上来  你还有什么发现
Now you going backwards. What else you got?
预测
Prediction.
-不会成功  -为什么?
- It won't come off. - Why is that?
-你得应付利比亚  -真的吗?
- You have to back off Lybia - Really?
但是  我不想在车内讨论
But, you dont want here this in a car...
好吧  给你个机会
All right, you get your shout.
明天十点见我
Meet me tomorrow for same ages at 10,
你要真是有勇有谋的话  就由你来操作这次交易
and tell me the guts little Shimark on it's right home. You structure this deals.
-你要做足准备  -听凭您的安排
- And you better be prepared. - I am on your disposal.
你不会真的住这里吧?
You don't really live here, do you?
斯巴达人的个头并不比美塞尼亚人大(英雄不问出身)
Well, the spartans won't bigger than mensenities.
是么  最终斯巴达人失败了
Yeah, and they eventurally get their asses kicked.
我没回家  想走走  一边走一边吸收  摄取
I didn't go in. I wanted to walk, move, digest, ingest.
你知道生命中有的时刻
There are moments in life, moments, when you know,
你只要跨过那座桥  便是新生
you crossed the bridge, you old life is over.
万隆是我的那座桥  我终于有了出头之日
van Loon was my bridge. Finally I had my shout.
华尔街也将成为我的垫脚石
Wall Street would be my steppingstone.
但我能走多远呢
But how far can I go?
首席执行官  跨国公司  甚至总统
CEO? A global force? Maybe president.
假以时日  我会叫世界震惊
Time cellody. Shook up the free world and got the things done.
突然
Suddenly,
思维再次跳跃
there was another skip.
我怎么走过20条街的
How had I gone the last 20 blocks?
又过了10条街  然后发现...
I get another 10 blocks. And then...
自己正走在市郊住宅区
I was way uptown.
这是哪一间酒吧
What bar was this?
打架?
A fight?
我不知道怎么打
I don't know how to fight.
或许知道?
or do I?
手这样架住他嘴巴
Set  her fingers in her mouth.
象这样
Like this.
攻击重要部位  眼睛  脖子  小腹
Attack vital Taek. Eyes, neck, intestines.
无论怎样  不要放弃  破坏他们的平衡
Whatever you do, do not end. Cut out the balance of your attacker.
集中力量攻击
disrupt the balance. Use the focus of your body.
当药效过去后
When it finally stopped.
我不记得在自己的生命中有那18小时
I couldn't account for the last 18 hours in my life.
是我  我还以为你会来
Hey, It's me. I thought you'd coming over.
你还好吗?  到家给我打个电话
Is everything okay? Call me when you get there.
我决定在不吃NZT的情况下看看万隆的文件
Even off NZT, I've decided to give Van Loon's files a shoot.
天书一般
They were hieroglyphics.
-你好  -凯文  我是爱迪
- Hello? - Kevin, this is Eddie.
听好  我不能来参加今天的会议
Listen, I can't make the meeting today.
你在说什么?
What you talking about?
我病了  今天不会来
I can not come today. I'm sick.
你现在不能感冒
You can't have the flu right now.
他们不会再给这样的机会
They never give this chance again.
我知道  听我说...
I know, listen. I just...
我看着这一切
I looked all this, otherwise.
你昨天都做什么了
What you've been doing last day?
凯文  我...
Kevin, I...
你明白吗  这是测试
Don't you get it? This is a test.
明白  但我现在过不了测试
Yes, well. I can't pass the test right now.
我如何知道你过不了
And how may I know if you don't.
-我理解  听我说...  -你听我说
- I know, listen. I just... - Listen to me...
振作精神  来开会
pull yourself together and get done to the meeting.
好吧  我会去的
OK, ok. I'll be there, I'll be there.
-你好吗  爱迪  -很高兴再次见到你
- Hi. How are you? Eddie? - Good to see you again.
坐
Sit down.
-你知道些什么关于汉克・埃德伍德?  -埃德伍德...
- What do you know about Henk Ed Wood? - Ed Wood...
他是个不因循传统的人
He is an iconoclast...
拥有半个科罗拉多州
owns about half of Colardo.
这就是你准备的  爱迪?
This is prepare, Eddy?
这是埃德伍德专题讨论?  每个人都了解他吗
Is this Ed Wood one on one? And does everybody know about Ed Wood.
两年前他在哪
Where was he two years ago?
不知道在哪
Nowhere.
两年前  福布斯排行榜还没有他
Two years ago, he wasn't even on Forbes' radar.
这是一个极大的飞跃  对吗?
This is a great big forward, right?
我落后于这个家伙
I'm backward this guy,
不知从哪儿冒出来的
comes out nowhere, so strong...
甚至在我安插人进他的公司前就已经很强大了
has been on the run before I could even get anybody in his camp.
将我挤出了最大两家企业之列  是北半球最好的公司
beats me out of two properties, best companies in the north...
我们面前的这间酒店
We are in the front of the hotel where a woman...
昨晚在房间内发现一名女性死者  确认为玛丽亚・温伯格
identified as Maria Vinberg, found dead last night in the room.
警方审问了酒店的员工几个小时
Police interrogated for several hours Employees at the hotel.
目击者曾看到受害者与一名男子在一起
witness saw a man together with the victim.
我们要怎么说服他  有什么主意?
How can we convince him to be in this game, got any ideas?
你怎么看
What do you think?
我想你跟他们不一样
I guess you're not one of those guys, are you? Eddy.
你会被电视分散注意力?
We lose you if there's a screen in the room?
世界在旋转  时间在流逝
There are tectonic plates which are shifting right under us.
稍等会儿
Hold on, one second.
这可能吗  我杀了人?
Was it possible? Could I've kill someone.
是我做的吗
Was it even me?
爱迪  是梅利莎
Edi? This is Melissa.
弗恩是否给了你一些东西  那些东西很危险
Did Veron give you something? Since these things are dangerous.
梅利莎
Melissa?
能见个面吗?  我要和你谈谈
Can we meet somewhere I have to talk to you.
我们正在谈
We talking now.
不  我们下午在比利餐厅见面吧
No, let meet at Billys on afternoon.
爱迪  我不能
Edi, I can't.
来吧
Please, come.
这很重要  我真的想知道你说的那个东西
This is important. I really need to know what you talking about.
然后我意识到  还有一些人知道NZT的存在
I realized that there were other people, who might now about NZT.
弗恩的其他客户
Vernon's other clients.
你好  我找杰瑞・布兰登
Yeah, hi. Can I talk to Jerry Braden?
杰瑞住院了
Jerry is in hospital.
-为什么?  -他精神不太好
- What is it? - Yea, he is not doing well at all.
你好  保罗・卡普兰是吗?
Hello. Paul Kaplan is there?
不在  保罗三天前去世
It is not. Paul died three days ago.
我的天  抱歉
God! Sorry.
他开始是头痛  然后在工作中昏倒
He started getting headaches, then he collapsed at work.
现在还住在重症监护室
Now he is in ICU.
祝他早日康复  谢谢
Wish him all the best. Thanks.
我拨出的寻人电话
Of all the people I called...
三个死了  其余的都病了
three were dead, and the rest were sick.
你好
Hello.
哪位
Hello?
快开  快
Go! GO!
爱迪
Eddie.
梅利莎
Melissa.
不要告诉我  "我看起来不错"  我知道不好
Do not tell me that I look good, Because I know.
我不想你看到这样的我
I did not want to see me this way.
你看起来不错
You look good.
是的  我设法改变我的生活
Yes, I sorted to get myself together.
NZT会对你产生效果的
NZT will do that to you.
-什么意思?  -我也服用过
- What do you mean? - I mean I took it too.
-弗恩没告诉你更多  对吧  -没告诉
- Vernie didn't tell you this, did he? - No.
当他告诉我这药时  我想一探其中的秘密
When we he told me about this new drug I was like down the hedge...
确实让我惊讶
and it was amazing.
我在45分钟内读完布赖恩・格林的《优雅的宇宙》
I read Brian Green's The Elegant Universe in 45 minutes.
而且我看懂了  明白了
and I understood it.
我的工作效率一夜之间忽然增长
My productivity has increased the sharply overnight.
我上司开始嫉恨我
And my boss started to hate me.
当我取得他的职位后感到害怕
They offered me his job. Then I got scared.
-为什么?  -因为我还没有笨到
- Why? - Why. Because I am not stupid.
相信一个人的大脑能在完全活跃的情况下而不出问题
Nobody can operate at that level of mental activity and not crush.
我停止了服用
I stopped taking it.
-然后?  -然后我病了
- And? - And I got sick.
头疼  作呕  因此我回去找弗恩
Headaches, throwing up. So I went back to Veron.
他告诉我服用过的人  都死去了
He talked me about alle the people that would die.
-你吃了多少了?  爱迪  -很多
- How much you've been taking? Eddie. - I'm taking a lot.
也许他们改良了
Maybe, maybe they worked out bugs.
也许是不同的种类
Maybe it's different batch.
是的
Yes.
-你现在停药了  对吗?  -先说完经过
- You off it right now, aren't you? - Just finish the story.
我停药后没死
I didn't take anymore and I didn't die.
一段时间后我意识到
After a time I realized that...
自己无法集中精神超过10分钟
I can't concentrate on  to anything longer than 10 minutes.
爱忘事  懒的动  行动迟缓
I missed deadlines, got lazy, slow, so slow.
那是两年前的事
That was two years ago.
到现在都没有好转
I haven't been the same since.
你还有药片么?  很好
You have some left? Good.
回家就吃  减少剂量  不要一下子停药
You go home and take it, reduce the dose, don't just stop,
若直接停药  你会死
You'll die, if you just stop.
试着摆脱掉它  否则  头痛只是个开始
Try to take if off. Otherwise, the headaches are just beginning.
我得走了
I have to go.
-你知道是谁生产的吗?  -我不知道
- Do you know who produces them? - I do not know.
我得走了
I have to go.
-倒霉  -听着  听着  听我说
- Oh, shit! - Listen, listen. Listen to me.
-你把我忘了是吗?  -没有
- You forget about me? - No.
我约了你十二点
12:00 and you were not here!
-我现在在这里  -好
- I am here now. - Good.
-跟我来  -我可以写支票给你
-Come forward. -I can write a chque.
支票  你精神不正常?
Chque! Chque! Are you out of your mind?
你认为我是什么  融资机构?
What do you think I am? Some financial institutions?
你说得对  我去银行提给你
You're right. Maybe I just go to the bank.
哪儿弄来的东西?
Where did you got that?
-这是什么?  -阿司匹林
- What is it? - It's just aspirin.
我还没有见过这样的阿司匹林
I have not seen such aspirin.
这是好东西  对吗?
It's something good, hum?
我感觉很爽  这东西有什么成份?
I feel good, man. What's in this stuff?
就是维他命和阿司匹林
It's just errr... vitamins with aspirin.
少胡扯  爱迪
Holy shit, Eddie baby.
琳达  我阻止不了他冲进来
Lindi, he is not allowed to enter, but I could not stop him.
-泰勒  我必须挂了  -我病了
- Tyler, I have to go. - I'm sick.
对不起  我坚持不到回家
I'm sorry! I couldn't make it home.
-我送你去医院  -不要
- You go to the hospital. - No, no, no...
我希望你能为我做些事情  我需要服药
I want you to do something for me. I need my pills.
-爱迪  什么样的药  -亲爱的  这很复杂
- Eddie, what kind of pills? - Honey, it's complicated.
你吃的什么药  你在服毒品?
What did you take? Are you on drugs?
我别无选择  把事情向琳达和盘托出
I had no choice. I told Lindi everything.
这么说你旺盛的精力  过人的专注都是因为这药?
So all these energy of yours, all this focus has been a drug?
我还以为它是被认可的
I thought it was approved.
我还藏起了一些
I have a supply stash.
-你想我去帮你拿  -不  我去取
- You want me to go get it. - No, I'm gonna go get it.
给我你公寓的钥匙  我去拿
Give me your keys. I go to the apartment.
它不在我的公寓  放在别的地方了
It's not in my apartment. I moved them.
放在哪儿了?
Ok. So where did you move it?
在我家里
In my house.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
-你拿到了?  -是的
- You got it? - Yeah.
有人跟踪我
There someone following me.
-你确定?  -确定
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
他的计程车一直跟着我的计程车
He got into a cab behind me and he's making every turn I'm making.
亲爱的  报警
Baby, call the cops.
能绕过去吗
Can you got around him?
-发生什么事  -塞车
- What happened? - We stopped.
他从车里出来了
He is getting out...
爱迪  他正走过来
Eddie, he is walking over here.
琳迪
Lindi.
我的天
Oh, god!
救命
Help!
这个人在追我  从我家一直跟到这
This man is chasing me. He followed me from my building.
我不认识他  帮帮我
I don't know him. Please!
离她远一点
Leave her alone.
你聋了吗?  我说  别靠近她
Are you deaf? I said, leave her alone!
哥们  你是不是要惹我?
Buddy, are you trying to piss me off?
你做什么  伙计?
What are you doing, man?
-你还在吗  -在  我在  -你不要说话  不要动
- Are you still there? - Yeah, I'm here. What happen?
-我困在这了  他会找到我的  -别说话  也别动
- I'm stuck. He'll find me. - Ok, stop talking and don't move.
-他杀死了两个人  -什么?
- He killed two guys. - What?
-他会杀了我  -不  不会的
- He's gonna kill me, too. - No, no, no.
你能看到他吗
Can you see him?
还不能
No, not yet.
我不知道该怎么做
I do not know what to do.
你打开袋子  吃一颗药丸
I need you to open the bag and take one of those pills.
为什么
Why?
因为吃了之后你就会知道该怎么办
because you know what to do. You take it then you know.
他有刀  爱迪  我想不出摆脱的法子
He has a knife, Edi. I can't think my way out of a knife.
那药30秒发挥作用  相信我
Just listen to me, it come out in 30 seconds.
到时候你就知道怎么做
And you think your way out. That's what it does.
他越来越近了
He is getting closer.
琳达  我爱你
Linda, I love you.
回到我这来
Now get back to me.
发生了什么事
What happened?
爱迪  亲爱的  一切会好起来
Edi, my dear. It's gonna be ok.
你得离开这里
You got get out here.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
对于发生的一切  我很抱歉
I'm so sorry for everything that happened.
我想让你知道  这些事情不会再次发生
I want you to know you that you'll never ever have to go thourgh this again.
因为现在我可以保护你
Cause I can take care of us now.
我相信你可以
I'm sure you can.
我们会很安全  我回来了
I can make it safe. I'm back, ok?
-谁回来了  爱迪?  -我
- Who is back? Eddie. - Me.
不  这不是你  你跟之前不同
No! It's not you. You were different before.
我仍然是同一个人
I am still the same person.
不是的  我也吃过所以我知道
I wasn't when I was on it.
我做了这辈子都不可能再做的事
I did things that I would never do.
但这东西救了你的命
Those things saved your life.
-但那不是我  -是你  不是你是谁
- But there weren't me. - Yes. There were, nor the where was.
我知道药效是怎样的
I know how it workes.
我懂  我完全理解  你觉得自己无所不能
I get it, I totally get it. you fell invincible.
它所能带给我们的是你无法想像的
Where it will take us that you can't even imagine.
我们能够做的事情
The things we will be able to do.
一年后我们会在哪里
Where we will be in a year from now.
我们将会过怎样的生活
What kind of life that we'll finally be able to live?
没有我你也能靠它生活
Will you might live it without me?
我会停止服用的
Look, I'll stop taking them.
有些事必须要做  以保证我们安全
There are some things I need to do to keep us safe and then set us up.
之后我不会再服用  这是我的计划
And then I gonna get off it. That's the plan.
我有计划  我发誓会停止服用
I have a plan. I swear I'm gonna get off it.
我希望你能做到
I hope you do.
在监视我吗
Looking for me?
你认为你可以逃避出我掌心吗?
You think you can run away from me?
你认为我不知道你是谁?
You think, I dont know who you are?
我相信我们的交易已经结束了
I was under the impression, our business is finished.
给我药  不然就地做了你
Well I wish some more of this stuff, or I shoot you right here.
然后照张相
And take a pic.
我摆脱不了这家伙
This guy was not gonna go away.
几片药可以应付他一段时间
A few pills would buy me some time.
-给你  两清了  -不一定
- Here it is. We're done. - We'll see.
直至我找到一个...  永久的解决办法
Until I found a more... permanent solution.
除非看到真正有威胁的人
Unless you see a real threat I never wonna know...
否则我不想让人知道我有保镖
that I have any security.
你们不要注视我  但要一直跟着
You never perceive me. You'll always follow me.
永远不要在15步以外徘徊
Never wander 15 steps behind.
互相也不要太靠近
And never stand to close together,
如果发生什么  我希望能够看到身后的情况
I wonna be able to look behind me if the opportunity persents itself.
不要穿同样颜色的西装  这不是黑客任务
And don't wear the same color of suit. This isn't the matrix!
爱迪  你要知道  我曾经找过你
You have to know Eddie, I wrote you up.
-我病了  -你不能病
- I was sick. - You don't get sick.
当你到达我这个级数时  就算给车撞了也不能死
You playing at this level, you get hit by a car you don't even die.
-你是绝对正确的  -我知道我是对的
- You're absolutely right. - I know I'm right.
那天我甚至不知道在跟谁  或跟什么在交谈
I mean, I didn't know who or what I was talking to.
跟摄氏40度(的我)在交谈
105, that your talked to, believing in.
-我修定了我的推测  -我没问你推测
- I sent over revised projections. - I didn't ask your projections...
我知道  但是我觉得  假如你能看看
I know, but I think If you look at them...
我已经看了  事实上有问题
I already have. There is matter in fact.
我解雇了项目组的一些人
I fired a few people over here projections.
-我很抱歉  -不用抱歉
- I'm sorry. - No, you're not.
你很不平凡  你注意到一些我的团队忽略的事情
You reliefed, you know things that my team has missed.
有那么一刻我曾想过这是真的吗
The minute, the instant... That's no longer true?
2个月后我开始服用NZT
Two months after I started NZT.
我已是公司史上最大企业合并的中间人
I was brokering the biggest merger in corporate history.
讽刺的是  这么做肯定残酷  残酷到让人憎恨
Ironically, it's gonna be cruel, cruel just gonna be the word hates me.
预期收益增长200%
Which is your expected profit by 200 percent.
我们所有人都会很高兴
And makes both of us are very happy chambers.
我发现如果我准时服用相同份量
I found out that if I take the same dose remember to eat,
不喝酒  就不会有问题
drink no alcohol the blackouts didn't occur.
汤姆  能帮我加个暗袋吗
Tom, is it possible to construct a secret pocket?
-这件西装?  -所有的西装
- On this? - In all of them.
当然可以  先生
Certainly, sir.
现在药片有了妥善的存放处
My Supplies is now safe,
我得注意药片的供应了
I had to take care that it doesn't run out.
我可以用相同的成份进行调配
I can combine these ingredients in the same relation,
很难说是否有相同效果
but the reaction on the brain...
没法预期
Dark, it's dark work.
-你的意思是?  -临床实验  白老鼠  人体试验
- Meaning? - Needs clinical experiments. guinea pigs, people.
那需要很长时间
It would take too long.
制药就是这样的  否则可能药死人
This is what it is. Otherwise, you kill people.
这需要12-18个月
You need 12-18 months.
如果你能在6个月内完成  我给你2百万美元
I'll give you two million dollars If you can do it in 6.
这可能需要花费30%
It could cost you 30%.
不好意思离开会儿
Execuse me for one second.
我以为我已经没有麻烦了  探长先生
I thought we straightend this up, detective.
这不是关于弗恩的  莫拉先生
This isn't about Veron again, Mr. Morra.
那关于什么?
And what is this about?
温伯格案的嫌疑人  是这个人吗
The suspect in the case of Vinberg, is this person?
想告诉我4月2日的晚上你去过哪里吗
You want tell me where about at night April 2nd?
我自己摆平不了这事
I couldn't keep this quite on my own.
布兰特・莫里斯  纽约最昧良心的律师
Brant Morris, the most lethal lawyer in New York.
你真幸运  有人打扫过房间
You are lucky, somebody wiped the room.
这是案例中最不具说服力的证据
In the best case, These are unconvincing evidence.
跟我说实话  当时你在那里吗
Just between us, were you there?
我不记得
I don't remember.
卡尔・万隆和汉克・埃德伍德还不知道..
Karl van Loon and Henk Ed Wood they had no idea...
我可能很快会被控谋杀罪
that I could soon be charged with murder.
赛科普和另一家正在竞争
But Cicorps and another are jacking...
同一个利比亚工业特许权
for the same industrial concession in Lybia.
我们公司假装不知情  不问此事
Both of our companies are pretending, we are not sniffing out.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know this?
政府的贿赂导致自身腐败堕落
The governmental bribes system is itself corrupt.
任何东西都可以买
So course, information, banks working. Like Anything can be bought.
继续
Go on.
如果你看看2008年左下方的柱状图
If you take a look at the lower left column in 2008,
在我们注意到之前
five companies were jacking for premission...
已有5家公司的许可权被收购
before we even took notice.
我的天  他看起来很苍老
Jesus, he looks froze.
-可能是假装的  -他还不到60岁
- Could be an act. - He is not even 60.
爱迪  有决定了?  打算怎么办
So have you decided, Eddie? What you gonna do.
-这件事已经结束了?  -我不知道
- This is over? - I do not know.
-你没有给我答案  -你还没有问
- You haven't give me the answer. - You haven't ask the question.
鉴于我的能力和贡献  45怎么样
Well, given the skill and my contribution, let's say 45.
4万5千美元?
$ 45,000?
4千万是一大笔钱
40 million is bloody, Eddie. It's a lot more without control.
爱迪  你要知道
You know, Eddie,
你可能会认为你不需要为我工作了
you might think that you will not work for me anymore.
我学到了很多
It was a useful experience.
我希望如此  但这并不意味着你有足够的经验
I hope so. I hope that does not mean you have enough of me.
与我斗
Armed to the next...
为了个人职业生涯的发展  我必须前进
Well, in order for a career to evolve, I have to move on.
你所表现出的一切告诉我
And that you even think that, shows me...
你没有想过做好准备自己干
you won't be prepared to be on your own.
我意思是说  你要知道你不平凡
I mean, you do know, you're a freak.
这是上帝的礼物  是运气  或是家族遗传
Your way is a gift from God or luck or biological heritage.
是礼物  不是挣得的
A gift. not earned.
你不知道我所知道的  因为你还没有那些经验
You do not know what I know, because you have not earned those powers.
当你有经验后会灭掉我们
You'll kill us with those powers.
你象个孩子一样不知道珍惜
You throw them around like a child.
你没有走过不公平的路
You did not have to climb up an uneven path.
你没有辛苦存集过资金
You have not collected the funds.
你没有娶过可以让你少奋斗30年的妻子
you haven't done the time that first merriage a girl with the right father.
你只是认为你可以
You think you can go over all this.
你不曾收买  迷惑或威胁人  以此来提升你的职位
You haven't bribed, charmed or threaten your way to sit at that table.
你从没有过竞争经验  因为你还没有竞争过
You never experienced competition, because you haven't competed.
不要让我成为你的的竞争对手
Don't make me your competition.
我开个价给你  你可以买些想要的玩具
Now I'll open up a line of credit for you. You've been wanted your few "toys".
酒店客房不再是一个合适的选择
Hotel rooms were no longer an option.
我需要住在保险柜里面
What I needed, was a bunker.
该建筑以安全为重心  中央控制
The building was constructed in a safe, central control,
钢门加上气压锁
armored doors with air lock.
这是3层式非并行安全系统
It's unparellel 3 tier security system.
堡垒般的景观
Fortress with a hell of a view.
-要价多少?  -850万美元
- What is the asking price? - 8.5 million.
我要了
I'll take it.
很明显  他是冲着NZT而来的
Right away, it was obvious , he was on NZT.
下星期  我要20颗
Next week, I gonna need 20 pills.
去你MD下星期
Next week, you can go fuck yourself.
不要说你有什么感觉
Not that you feel anything.
我不认为你想让金融界朋友们知道
I don't think your fortune 500 finacial friends...
你跟警察之间那点小尴尬的细节
would appreciate the details of your little dilemma with the police.
星期四  我会在这等药丸
Thursday, I am gonna need the pills here.
变聪明了呢
Getting smarter...
显然  这不能再继续下去
Obviously, this can not go on.
但这是世界上一小部份
But there is very little on this earth...
4千万美元也解决不了的事
that 40 million dollars can't solve.
埃德伍德明天9点签署文件
Tomorrow at 9:00, Ed Wood would sign the papers.
要打电话给他吗
Do you wonna call them?
-伤风?  -昨晚是那么说的
- Coryza? - It's all last night for tell us that.
-有回话吗  -我会再打一次  先生
- Anything? - I call again, sir.
决定也许会改变  没必要卑躬屈膝
Okay, the decision could change. That make sense that's the curtsy doesn't.
等一下吧
It's still on.
纯粹是你的预测?
Oh, basing on your charts and projections?
也许你应该提醒我  你是谁?
Maybe you remind me, who are you anyway?
对不起  卡尔  这家伙惹我反感
I'm sorry, Karl. this guy is pissing me off.
-他的态度...  -丹纳姆  收回你的话
- Because the... - Dunham, pull it back.
打扰了  万隆先生  埃德伍德夫人在您的办公室
Excuse me. Mr. Van Loon, Missis Ed Wood is in your office.
埃德伍德夫人  我是卡尔・万隆  这是我的同事莫拉先生
Mrs. Ed Wood. Karl Van Loon. My associate, Mr Morra.
幸会
Pleasure.
-我想让这件事尽可能的保密  -当然
- I wanted to make this as confidental as possible. - Of course.
我丈夫今早感到头痛  头晕
My husband has experienced some pain and dizziness this morning.
他正在接受观察和体检
He is currently analyzed, and going tests.
我只是想让你知道  我们非常希望签署这个合同
I just want you to know we have every intention of signing the contract.
一旦他恢复正常  我们就继续进行
And as soon as he is able, we will proceed.
我知道这是陈词滥调  但如果有任何需要
I realize that this is a useless platitude, but if there is anything we can do...
随时告诉我们
dont't hesitate to tells us.
我们乐意为您提供任何帮助  埃德伍德夫人
We want to provide you with any help, ma'am Ed Wood.
先生们  谢谢  我会记住你们的好意
Thank you, gentlemen. I relay on your digression.
或许是另一个手段
There would be approximate.
为了变卦放弃权利?
A person like him giving away the power for turning?
希望他早日康复
Hope he will get better.
但埃德伍德没有好转  因为他没有NZT了
But Ed Wood wouldn't get better. Because Ed Wood was out of NZT.
我为什么惊奇
Why would me surprised?
有多少成功人士是依靠NZT的
I wonder how many other successful people might be explained by NZT?
至少我仍有一些药  生命还没受到威胁
At least I had some. My life wasn't in jeopardy.
我们到了
And we at here.
我要的是钱和自由
Only my money, and my liberty.
我们准备好了
I've been all over them.
他们无论种族  身材  衣着
We can not allow any disparity in race or physical type.
都与你极度相似
between you and the rest of the suspects.
看起来跟你的复制品差不多
they are close to your clones as its possible as you could get.
就好像是同一个大帅哥  模糊难辨
It's gonna be just one big handsome blur's guy.
玻璃后面的是谁?
Who was out there?
那个女人的丈夫?
Woman's husband?
酒店女工?
Hotel maid?
事情会怎么结束?
Was this how it's going to end?
没确定  他昏头了
Nothing in this clue, he was dizzying.
"右边数第三个  不  不是他"
"He was the third from the right. No, not him." Here you go.
很好的西装  量身订做的吗
This thing is a beauty. custom-made?
是的
I did.
市场推测万隆合伙人正在跟汉克・埃德伍德
Market speculates today. The doubt has been yo-yo in this speculation at...
谈判有关合并的事宜
Van Loon associates and Henk Ed Wood are negotiating about a merge.
你有向别人提及过吗?
Have you been talk to anyone?
我没有跟任何人谈起过  卡尔  我又不傻
I haven't been talk to anybody, Karl. I'm not stupid!
我知道你不傻  但聪明的人多会犯一些小错误
I know that you're not stupid but don't make the classic smart person's mistake.
你认为这里没人比你更聪明
Do you think that there is none smarter than you.
你究竟到哪里去了?
Where the hell have you been?
这是你第二次消失
This is the second time and the disappearance.
就在楼里喝咖啡  为什么问  我错过了重要时刻?
I was in the building. I was getting coffee. Why? Is it been a moment?
是的  重要时刻  埃德伍德陷入昏迷状态
Yes, It's been a moment alright. Ed Wood is in a coma.
他没有耍我们  而是快死了
He wasn't playing us, he is dying.
关于这件事你都知道些什么?
What do you know about this?
我当时可不象平时那般有问必答
I was less than usually equipped answer.
我意识到早就应该吃NZT了
I noticed, that I was overdue to take my NZT.
疼痛是从眼睛后面开始的
And the pain was starting behind my eyes.
稍等
Excuse me.
不要逃避
You are not excused.
卡尔  你的员工解手也不行?
Your employees aren't allowed to take a piss, Karl?
律师  警察  还是更衣室的人拿去了
It was Brant, or someone else the police station, cloakroom.
莫拉先生...
Mr Morra...
莫拉先生  您有一个包裹
Mr Morra! This just came for you.
我再问你一次  爱迪  你知道些什么?
I ask you again, Eddie. What do you know about this?
-关于消息走漏?  -不是  关于埃德伍德
- What about? The leak? - No, about Ed Wood.
关于埃德伍德些什么?
What about Ed Woodu?
想骗我  你还不够老道
You got a long way to go as a liar.
卡尔  我不知道这些...
Karl, I do not know what...
听  你所说的都是废话
Listen, what you about to say is bullshit!
我知道你是隐藏了些什么的  我已经察觉到了
There is something you hiding from me, I smell it on you!
现在  我想知道这笔交易怎么就作废了
Right now, I want to know why is this cluster fuck of deal is dead in the water!!
爱迪
Eddie!
今天  在莱诺克斯山医院附近
Today, near the Lennox Hill Hospital today,
更多关于万隆跟埃德伍德合并的传言流出
more twisting terms about van Loon - Ed Wood merger.
关于这次合并的谣传绝对不具真实性
There is absolutely no truth to the rumor of this merger.
不论怎么说
None whatsoever.
我丈夫还在医院接受检查  对我们来说这是个困难的时刻
My husband is having tests and it's a difficult time.
如果各位将更多的问题留待下次提出  我将非常感激
We would be appreciate you directing further questions to our returning.
目前没有更多的消息
Err, yes. We have no further comments at this time.
我们正在等待艾德伍德先生的检验结果
We are waiting for results of Ed Wood's test,
并希望是最好的结果
and hoping for the best.
爱迪  我知道你在里面
Eddie, I know you're there, Eddie.
出来吧
Come out.
快点
Come on!
打开门
Open the door.
所以我在这里
And so, here I am.
我知道他们会用可怕的方式慢慢地将我杀死
I knew that they will kill me slowly and horrible.
但跳楼至少是我的选择
But this choice would at least be mine.
然而求生是生物的本能
But we are instinct creatures.
我想活下去
We want to live.
我混乱的大脑试图记起
so my foggy brain tried to remember...
在什么地方还有一颗NZT
where one tablet of NZT might be...
有可能的
It was possible,
"有可能"就足够了
and possible was enough.
爱迪
Hi, Eddie.
你知道我需要更多  为什么要让我失望
You know, I want more, so why would you upset me?
我讨厌使用最后一份
I don't like being dumped of this last one.
你还不知道如何有效使用它们
You do not even know how to use it.
我把它们溶解
You see, I have dissolved a solution.
直接注射
You shoot it.
药物直接进入血液和大脑
It goes right into the blood and brain.
持续得更久
It lasts much longer.
你打算告诉我其它的药在哪吗?
Are you gonna tell me where the rest is?
不  没这打算
No, probably not.
给我搜
这些家伙会找到的
You know, these guys are gonna find it...
我也会想法让你说
Or I gonna make you tell me.
问题是  哪种方式先找到
The question is, which is gonna come first.
看来  要探讨一番
I guess, we'll find out.
这是浪费时间
This is a waste of my time, you know.
我也不想再做这些事
And I am gefting out of this side of the business...
正在张罗进出口贸易公司
I'm starting import-export company.
这些都是非常让人兴奋的东西
Very exiting stuff.
我给你带来了很多工具  你真幸运
I got a lot on my plate, you're lucky I am here.
这里有个保险箱
要是以前我可能会剥你的皮  活剥了你
Back in the old times. I might peel your skin back, flay you.
剥皮  多美的词儿  我以前都没注意到
Flay. That's a nice word, I didn't notice before.
我的词汇真匮乏
I had such a poor vocabulary.
但后来我发现一样东西: 谷歌
But then I discovered this thing: Google.
你知道人的结肠有20英尺长吗?
Did you know that the colon is 20 foot long?
我不知道  也不相信
I had no idea, I don't believe it.
这回要亲眼看看  谁让我好奇心重呢  这个词儿也不错
I gotta see this for myself. I am dubios. It's another nice word.
我敢肯定  你也很好奇
Anyway. I am sure you're curious too.
不要担心  都消过毒了
Do not worry, everything is sterilized.
我会留住你性命  好增加一点乐趣
I gonna keep you alive for the whole fun.
我会保留你的小弟弟
You gonna get a reserved place in front, baby!
没有太多的尝试和挣扎  因为我也会死在这里
Not much of a try and fuzzy. because I would die here too.
只有NZT可以帮到我
only NZT could help me...
但剩下的  已溶解在这死人的血液中
and the last one was in this pug's bloodstream.
维克多
Victor!
什么?
What?
我看不到任何东西
I do not see anything!
射你的右手边
维克多
Victor!
警方认为先前的屋主
The police will later know that my appartment privious owner...
是个军火商
was an arms dealer.
有一些不满意的客户来报仇  很正常
Of course with some disstatisfied clients.
夜晚才刚刚开始
And the night was still young.
我敢肯定你想知道  你的老板发生了什么事
I'm sure you're curious about What happened to your boss.
我肯定
I certainly am.
如果我的转变真的能够为拯救埃德伍德先生的生命有用
I mean if my turning was really working for saving Mr. Ed Wooda's life,
他为什么死了?
Why is he dead?
我的意思是他将自己的生命寄托在药物上的意义是什么
I mean what point was the point to expressible riding with his life sitting medication?
他老板死了
His boss was dead.
所以我不再是他的问题
So I didn't matter now.
但是他并不欣赏我的律师偷了药后私藏起来的举动
But he didn't appreciate that Moris Brant had kept the pills for himself.
再一次万事皆有可能
And it was all still possible.
12个月后
事实上  没有更多门票了
Actually there're no more tickets.
是的  我知道  提前预定的资助人优先
Yes, I know. And over booked fund raisers at first.
他来了  我会问他
Well, here he comes. I'll ask him.
-好多了  做得好  -谢谢您
- Oh, that's much better. Great job! - Thank you, sir.
爱德华
Edward.
我看过第二溢出带
I taken a looking at second overflowed band.
有一笔巨资打算汇入  他们想保持价位
A wave of donations is coming in. And all are just happy to keep their money.
太好了
Great.
等等  有个自称是艾文公司的人在办公室内等你
Hold on. A guy from Iven Camcorps in your office.
我午餐有约
I have a lunch.
你距离出席赞助商的活动还有两分钟
You have two minutes yet for your main sponsor.
-艾文药业公司?  -是的
- Iven Camcorps pharmaceuticals? - Yes.
终于遇到了一位愿意亮相的
Finally meet the guy who keeps the lights on.
-卡尔?  -莫拉先生
- Karl? - Mr. Morra.
真是意外
What a surprise!
他们告诉我  有人来自艾文
They told me that someone comes from Iven ...
是的  我打算退出能源工业
Yes, thats me now. I am moving out of the energy business.
不会吧
Come on!
这好比赫夫纳退出夜总会似得(不可能)
That's like Hefner move out of the mansion.
几个月前我买了艾文药业  我很惊讶你还没听说
I bought Iven several months ago. I'm surprised you didn't hear.
没听说  我这里很忙
No, no! Well... I gonna keep me up here.
是收获的时候了  莫拉参议员
That's gonna pay off, Senator Morra.
参议员  谁估计的到?
The Senate... Who knows?
这能让事情发展得更顺利  对吗爱迪?
Anything is possible from here, isn't it, Eddie?
你我都知道  你能维持这种状态的关键是什么
I think we both know where it's heading if you can maintain.
你有没有想过  药吃完后怎么办?
Have you asked yourself, what you gonna do when you run out?
-你都知道些什么  -这有关系吗  反正我就是知道了
- What did you know? - Does it matter? I know now.
若你提早找我的话
I wish you'd come to me at first, Eddie.
便可以用33美元的股价购买艾文的股票
I could have bought Iven at 33 a share.
我们会是合作伙伴
We could have been partners.
所以NZT是艾文制造的
So Iven makes NZT.
它永远不会正式存在
Well. It'll never officially exist.
当然  你具有的有利条件无需多说
Obviously, I don't need to point out the advantages for you.
我觉得你也许应该说说
Oh I think, maybe you do.
无限量的供应  但你再也得不到
Unlimited supply. We know, you can't get anymore.
你肯定?
Are you sure about that?
我今早关闭了你的实验室
I shut down your lab this morning.
爱迪  我只想帮助你
Eddie, I just want to help you, that's all.
继续供应你  不会让你心烦意乱  记在心里就好
Keep your supply, no distraction service. Give a piece of mind, that's all.
我需要做些什么作为回报?
In return I do what?
也许给我点建议  我不会麻烦你太多
Give a little advice maybe, I won't be bother you much at first.
以后呢  会是什么事?
Later. What would bother me with?
有一些雄心勃勃的想法  我们认为是可行的
We have some ambitious ideas, We think that is achievable.
-若我不太喜欢你的主意?  -那只能祝你万事如意了
- And if I don't like your ideas? - Then, we'll say godspeed.
你的辉煌将会继续  但象烛光般短暂
And your candle will shatter brief of lovely light.
你不用现在答覆我  爱迪
Do you know what I mean? Eddie. Let's not go there right now.
目前我只想让你健康聪明
Right now, I just want to keep you brillant and healthy.
走吧  一起吃个午饭
Come on, let's go get some lunch.
您先请  参议员
After you, Senator.
谢谢你的支持  卡尔
Thanks for your stand by, Karl.
给我们一点时间
Give us a second.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你想当美国总统
Do you want to be president of United States?
还是脑血管阻塞  中风?
Or braindead, stuck full of tubes?
我会把握自己的机会
I'll take my chances.
你的机会不存在  我们已经关闭了你的实验室
I told you, your chance don't exist. We have shut down your lab.
难道你不认为一个能够创建NZT的天才
Don't you think the smartass who created NZT...
也许会有3-4间实验室
might have 3, 4 other labs?
那又怎样?  已没有工厂可以制造它了
So what. You're not making anymore.
没错  所以我找到了一个解决方案
That's right. I got something better.
我已重新设计  改良和修正了它
See once you know what's in it you can tweak, re-engineer, get the bugs out.
咱们各走各的  卡尔
I am off, Karl.
你无论如何都不会为我工作吗
Even so, there is no scenario you are not gonna work for me.
你打算怎么付我薪水?  用香烟
How you gonna pay me? In cigarettes?
-去年你有17次内幕交易  -你在威胁我吗?
- Last year you traded insider information 17 times. - You threating me?
来自迪拜的支票  对智利的倾销  消失不见的官员
Like cheques from Dubai, dumping in Chile, disappeared officals.
你想跟我对着干?
Do you want a war with me?
相信我  当我说这些的时候  可没有发挥想象
Trust me when I say this I am not even being creative.
你不能在给我安上一堆罪名后  还想活着离开
There's no way you can make accusations like that and walk out alive.
你怎么想是你的事  如果你想斗  我会准备好
Then you would even think that's yours. I want to prepare you want to fight me.
你根本没资格跟我斗
You are no longer equipt to fighe me.
你真的以为我什么都没学到?
Do you think I didn't learn anything?
以为我没有任何转变?
My story does not mention you on it?
你根本不知道我是个怎样的敌人
You have no idea what kind enemy I am...
货车会从后面撞上计程车
That van is going rear on that taxi.
什么?
What?
货车时速80公里  而司机正在发短信
The driver writes a text message and go 80 km per hour.
它一定会撞上18米外的一辆计程车
He must have points with braking at 18 meters from a taxi!
我看得到这一切  卡尔
I see everything, Karl.
我领先你50步  并领先于所有人
I'm 50 moves ahead of you and everybody else.
你怎么知道我身边没有能跟你竞争的人?
What make you think I don't have a guy with bid on you right now?
你如何能知道明年这个时候自己还活着?
How do you know that you will be alive next year this time?
你在干什么?  放开你的手
What are you doing? Put your hands off me!
心肌泵血力量只有正常的一半  应该是扩张型心肌病
Heart is pumping with half power Walls of your heart are dilated.
你需要一个人造心脏来维持大动脉的运作
Aorta is in motion. Soon you need this replaced.
你已经知道的
You already knew that.
你应该对此感到高兴
You know you should be glad about this.
若我来帮你做事  你只能当跟班
Cause me working for you, you'll end up as my bitch.
也许我们应该先冷静下来后再谈谈
Maybe we should cool off and talk again.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
不要忘了投票
Don't forget to vote.
爱德华  顺利吗?
Edward, you good?
嗯  跟你说了我约了人吃午餐
Yeah, told you I have a lunch.
-抱歉迟到了  -别在意
- I am sorry, baby. - Hey, don't worry.
-今天过得怎么样?  -不能更好了
- How's your day gone? - Perfect better.
我还是不习惯你这个发型
I still can't get used to this haircut.
我在街上可能都认不出是你
I wouldn't even recognize you on the street.
我已不是从前的我了
All I am a new man.
我已经点过餐了
I've already ordered.
担担面  2个猪油饼
Can I have Szechuan dandan noodle. 2 Crullers with lard.
青葱炒龙虾
Stir fried lobster with spring onion.
千万不要给我味精呀
I don't want MSG in any dishes.
围巾会保护你的衣服
Neck scarf will keep your suit clean.
可是保护不到我的脏爪啊
But it can't keep my hans clean.
干嘛这样看着我
What?